<resources>
    <string name="app_name">NudgeApp</string>
    <string name="accessibility_service_label">NudgeApp</string>
    <string name="accessibility_service_description">Nudging people towards better decisions in their usage of technology</string>

    <string name="preference_file_key">com.example.thesistest2</string>
    <string name="system_preference_file_key">com.example.thesistest2.myservice</string>

    <!--Strings used for notification-->
    <string name="channel_name">ThesisTestNotificationChannel</string>
    <string name="channel_description">Notification channel for displaying notifications</string>
    <string name="notification_title">NudgeApp</string>
    <string name="notification_message">NudgeApp is running in the background</string>
    <string name="notification_ticker_text">NudgeApp is running in the background</string>

    <!--Strings used for requesting permissions in xiaomi or Android > 10-->
    <string name="xiaomi_dialog_title">Enable permissions</string>
    <string name="xiaomi_dialog_text">This app will not work if you do not grant the permissions for displaying pop-up windows, even while running in the background.</string>
    <string name="give_permissions">Give permissions</string>
    <!--Strings used for displaying toasts related to permissions-->
    <string name="permissions_granted_message">Thank you for giving your permission.</string>
    <string name="permissions_not_granted_message">Give your permission or this app will not work.</string>

    <!--Strings in settings activity-->
    <string name="settings_label">Settings</string>
    <string name="switch_open_label">Use custom text for opening app</string>
    <string name="switch_back_label">Use custom text for closing app</string>
    <string name="custom_label">Write your custom label</string>
    <string name="preview">Preview</string>
    <string name="enable_accessibility_service">Enable service</string>
    <string name="enable_accessibility_service_explanation">This app needs you to manually enable an accessibility service from settings. Doing so, NudgeApp will be able to collect information about how you use Facebook, Instagram and TikTok, and provide nudges that will help you in making more conscious decisions while using technology. \nClick below -> Downloaded apps -> NudgeApp -> Enable</string>
    <string name="service_explanation_already_running">Service is already running. If you see a permanent notification from NudgeApp, everything is working correctly.</string>
    <string name="go_to_accessibility">Go to accessibility menu</string>


    <!--default strings for buttons -->
    <string name="open_button_label">Open app</string>
    <string name="back_button_label">Close app</string>


    <!--Strings containing textual nudges-->
    <string name="opening_app_label">You have chosen to open</string>
    <!--Nudge 1-->
    <string name="scroll_nudge1_1_facebook">Know that infinite scrolling is one the dark patterns used by Facebook for keeping you online and earning from your attention. You can keep scrolling as much as you want, but the reward you get is variable, since the quality of the new contents cannot be predicted.</string>
    <string name="scroll_nudge1_1_instagram">Know that infinite scrolling is one the dark patterns used by Instagram for keeping you online and earning from your attention. You can keep scrolling as much as you want, but the reward you get is variable, since the quality of the new contents cannot be predicted.</string>
    <string name="scroll_nudge1_1_tiktok">Know that infinite scrolling is one the dark patterns used by TikTok for keeping you online and earning from your attention. You can keep scrolling as much as you want, but the reward you get is variable, since the quality of the new contents cannot be predicted.</string>
    <string name="scroll_nudge1_2">Know that the infinite scrolling dark pattern used in social networks can lead you to a more passive and problematic technology overuse, causing lack of sleep, decreased communication, depression, or even obesity and ADHD. </string>
    <!--Nudge 2-->
    <string name="scroll_nudge2_1_fast">You have been scrolling fast recently. Slow down and enjoy the contents.</string>
    <string name="scroll_nudge2_1_really_fast">You have been scrolling really fast recently. Slow down and enjoy the contents.</string>
    <string name="scroll_nudge2_2_fast">You have been scrolling fast recently. If nothing is of your interest, consider taking a break.</string>
    <string name="scroll_nudge2_2_really_fast">You have been scrolling really fast recently. If nothing is of your interest, consider taking a break.</string>

    <!--Nudge 1-->
    <string name="pull_nudge1_1_facebook">Know that pull to refresh is one of the attention-capture dark patterns used in Facebook. It allows you to swipe down and load contents which can be new or not, as it happens in slot machines, where you can win or lose.</string>
    <string name="pull_nudge1_1_instagram">Know that pull to refresh is one of the attention-capture dark patterns used in Instagram. It allows you to swipe down and load contents which can be new or not, as it happens in slot machines, where you can win or lose.</string>
    <string name="pull_nudge1_1_tiktok">Know that pull to refresh is one of the attention-capture dark patterns used in TikTok. It allows you to swipe down and load contents which can be new or not, as it happens in slot machines, where you can win or lose.</string>
    <string name="pull_nudge1_2">Know that the pull to refresh dark pattern used in social networks can lead you to use more technology, causing lack of sleep, decreased communication, depression, or even obesity and ADHD. </string>
    <!--Nudge 2-->
    <string name="pull_nudge2_1">You have refreshed the contents. If you have already seen everything, just take a break.</string>
    <string name="pull_nudge2_2">Pull to refresh is like a slot machine. This time it’s a win or a loss?</string>

    <!--Strings used to detect pull gestures in home screen in social media-->
    <string name="text_pull_detection_facebook">facebook</string>
    <string name="text_pull_detection_instagram">story</string>
    <string name="app_icon_description">App icon</string>
</resources>